so bitcoin is crashing what to do now
what is going on so i'm gonna start off
by saying this
i am not a bitcoin expert i have called
everything that has happened with
bitcoin in the past six months it's
purely because of technical analysis i
am a purely technical analysis trader i
don't i'm not a bitcoin expert i'm not a
forex expert i guess you can say i'm a
forex success but just because i'm
full-time but like i have caught
everything on bitcoin based off of
market structure and what the charts are
showing bitcoin right now is actually at
22 000. tomorrow by the time i upload
this it could be at 10 000. a week from
now when you see this if you have 30
000. i don't know where it's going to be
at but what i'm going to be showing you
guys in the charts is exactly how i
predicted how price is going to get here
where i personally think it's going to
go and how long i think it's going to
personally take to go back to the
heights right so again i'm not a
financial advisor i'm strictly purely a
market structure trader and i purely
trade based off of market analysis that
doesn't mean that you know i don't
obviously know the fundamentals and all
the stuff when it comes to the bitcoin
but i mainly focus on the charts
everything that i have predicted up to
now has been based off of what i see on
the charts just completely erase the
fact that they're printing too much
money or they're stealing x amount from
certain blockchains forget about that i
literally have done everything based on
the charts so before i get into the
charts i want for those of you guys if
you guys are in the red right now i'm
gonna pop up a screenshot right here of
a token or like an altcoin that i
invested in that i'm literally 90
96 in drawdown like it does not get
worse than this might as well just
forget my passwords call the money lost
if you're in the red right now just set
and forget don't panic so because once
people are in panic that's when you want
to be greedy and you want to get into
the market once people are being greedy
and just too much setting and forgetting
that's when you want to be fearful and
just let them do their thing that's kind
of what happened when you know prices
were going up to like 60k everybody was
everybody in their mother knew about
bitcoin everybody was buying now
everybody's panicking literally today i
was talking to one of my buddies and um
he's a watch theater he's like bro and
the previous months i usually get
anywhere around seven to ten calls to
sell watches this week alone i've gotten
30 40 cops because people are just you
know panic they're scared they want to
recuperate from the losses so if you're
in the red right now set up forget if
you're not in the red lucky you i wish i
was you i wouldn't be 96 percent of
drama i would be buying right now
probably not right now not just yet
based on what you guys see on the charts
you guys kind of you know have an idea
of where i personally are going to be
more interested in going in i myself am
in the red big-time i don't have to sell
anytime soon i do believe crypto on the
long run will rise but for now this is
kind of part of my prediction so don't
panic so if you're in the red don't get
out just yet if you're looking to buy
don't buy just yet get in at the right
point get it at the right structure
point like you're already in a beautiful
spot whether you're getting into bitcoin
ethereum all coins that you're at a
point where even if price goes up to the
previous highs you're gonna minimum one
two extra month this is you know
something that's never been unheard of
but when we get into the charts i'm
gonna show you guys exactly what would
be the proper approach and i'm just
gonna show you guys how i do everything
based off of what i see to the left it's
very easy once you understand you know
market analysis and market structure
everything is right in front of your
face so um let's get into the start so i
show you guys exactly how i predicted
this whole entire drop and
i personally think again i'm not a
crypto expert but i am a full-time forex
trader so
the same market my this is my same
strategy applies to
any market in my opinion anything that
has technical analysis i believe that i
can trade and i have you know
statistically proven it so i generally
think um that i could predict the future
so let's get into the charts all right
guys so now that we're in the charts i'm
going to show you guys before i show you
guys a drop i'm going to show you guys
how easily i predicted the bull trend
right so let me show you guys um how i
predicted this bullish push right here
i'm gonna be completely blunt and honest
i did not predict this to go up this
high ever in my life i predicted for it
to come up to this structure point
because
i base my take profit of what i see to
the left so if you notice here there's
nothing else to the left so once we
would have uh let's say price would have
done something like this
once it was at a point like this i
identified this point right here as a
form of take profit i can't put this
point over here because there's
absolutely nothing like i'm basing this
because last time price came into 19 000
it rejected
i can't put 32 000 because it's never
been there i don't know how it's gonna
react so i place realistic take profits
i'm gonna be honest everything that i do
is from what i see i can't be one of
these wannabe gurus i say oh it's gonna
hit 25 when that thing has ever happened
at 25 right i know some people have take
profits of you know maybe a hundred
thousand which is realistic but there's
nothing showing you
um technical wise that it's gonna hit a
hundred everything i'm going to show you
is technical wise why i think it's gonna
hit x amount of points right
so while we were in um 2020 um it's kind
of when i uh was you know interested in
bitcoin you know i had you know some of
it not much just you know a couple
thousand other than that crazy but i did
uh you know
sadly take off all of my positions here
because this is where my take profit was
as you can tell here market structure at
one point was creating lower lows
and then as you can tell we then have a
higher high breaking out of this
ascending triangle for my
forex guys i don't really use uh sending
triangles but you can't help to notice
you know for bigger moves like this kind
of like bitcoin you could kind of you
know throw these ascending triangles
because you see how price could
basically bounce within this in here
right so you can obviously see that this
move right here as you can tell we not
only broke out of the triangle but most
importantly we broke out of the market
structure as you can see this is a point
that has been used as resistance as
resistance and i'm sure if i drag it out
to the left this is resistance and
support in the past as you can see here
the daily time frame has gone bullish by
breaking out of this zone
coming back retesting the same exact
zone as support then you have a bullish
engulfing rejection candle and then
basically the next point where you can
set a take profit would be at this point
right here why because it's the next
point where price rejected and then
obviously here notice it's not a
coincidence that the last time price
came into this point right here it
rejected notice how we kind of get into
the zone of the previous structure level
it was kind of slowing down notice how
the momentum to that point is purely
bullish candles as soon as we get close
to the resistance what do we get some
bearish candles obviously to have a
little bit retracements on the lower
timeframes but we obviously ended up
breaking through that so i just kind of
wanted to show you guys a little bit of
that show you guys how simple that is um
where are we now so right now we um
are at a lower low big time lower low as
you can tell we have
beautiful bullet structure we all know
this is where everybody and their mother
knew about bitcoin and now this is where
we went bearish and now we have a lower
low this is where i personally myself
predicted bitcoin was going to go to the
downside for me it was a very clear
indication because as you can tell on
the weekly time frame you have
a
higher high higher low higher high the
highest high that has been so meaning if
we break under this structure point
right here we are now bearish on the
weekly time frame so as you can see we
come down we break under this level
meaning now we have a lower low on the
weekly time frame this is where i would
wait for then a retracement to then come
back and re-test previous structure
level retest the weekly ema and then
also if you could potentially see it a
lot of you guys might not be able to see
it you're gonna kind of see the retest
of the neckline of the head and
shoulders along with ema and structure
right so you got like three four things
telling you this is heading to the
downside right obviously we kind of had
this little mess around here then we did
above a new higher high but as soon as
we bit as soon as we broke under this
lower low structure i knew we were going
to come all the way to 30 000 as you can
tell 30 000 is a respected support
everything that i'm going to point out
is literally what the market is showing
me right once we have identified the
market support structure i find wrong
psychological levels let me actually
round it off because this kind of gives
me anxiety i mean delete
zero zero point zero so we have round
psychological thirty thousand so i said
in my free telegram which the link is in
the link uh below i'm like as long as
you remain above 30 000 and this
structure point we are bullish
or we can have the potential to be
bullish right
what happened we then body close under
the zone and under the structure this is
a very simple concept when it comes to
trading it's
break and retest so head up
brake re-test when you're going down
it's the same brake resistance we're
coming back and we're re-testing this
structure level the same level that was
used as support
which would basically be this level
right here as you notice it can be this
exact same point right here
is then used as support again as you can
see it is used as support right here and
as you can tell it is used as support
right here so as you notice i'm pointing
out all of these points just obviously
on this line chart that i made once we
break under which would be this break
right here we then wait for the re-test
which is this retest right here and then
what do you expect the next lower low so
easy this to me was probably one of the
easiest trades i could have caught in in
my career i just personally don't trade
bitcoin just because for me it's just
too volatile i just rather not trade it
but i could you know predict the
technical analysis so once we had the
retest i think on the dailies where it
looks the cleanest yeah just look how
beautiful this looks on the daily
timeframe like if this isn't like a
screaming cell i don't know what is but
you have the lower low then you have the
beautiful daily double top rejection
from round psychological 30 000 you go
down to the four hour you have the whole
entire four hour shift i could get into
geek mode and you know you know get into
detail or we then have here the brick of
the structure on the four hour this
would have been our engine signal go
down to the one hour we then have the
retest of the support resistance we have
our bearish engulfing and so on right
that's all cool but you guys want to
understand what can possibly happen next
right so
for me this is bearish this is bearish
for me
into the next point of support what the
hell do i mean by that whenever price
drops it doesn't just drop and just stop
it and like just stop wherever it stops
at a point where it's respected in the
past as you notice here once we came
under whether we stop at a point where
we respected in the past where did we
have a retracement to a point where it
was respected in the past whether we
have a retracement to a point where
we're respected and so on and so forth
where do we reject we're respected
respected and i could go on with many
examples right so for me i personally
believe this is going to continue
dropping all the way up into this
structure point right here as you can
see this structure point right here
is used as resistance and resistance as
you can see once we came into the zone
we kind of slowed down a little bit and
then obviously some little hesitation
before we continue breaking out i
personally think there is nothing going
to stop this everybody's panic selling
everybody's kind of tripping out so i
think this is going to continue melting
just a little bit more until we get into
this area once it gets into this area
i'm not immediately buying i am not
doing that i need to wait for a
formation like this i need to get a
rejection confirmation
from the resistance the resistance i
need to get a rejection confirmation
from the resistance from the resistance
to be used as support so that i could
obviously look for buys to the upside
but even then the overall trend is still
bearish i could possibly be buying a
little retracement into this area here
once it comes back up to 30 000 then i
could continue heading to the downside
so i could be technically buying the
push but i could be having my take
profit let's say i get my entry signal
of buys here i could have my take profit
at this resistance so if price comes
into this area and then it rejects or
it's not looking that good to continue
heading to the upside then i simply sell
or i simply just get out of the position
and for whatever reason if price does
decide to then break above the 30 000
all right but now i'm just going to
simply wait for them the retracement to
then buy as you can see right here when
we broke above what did we do we came
back retested and buy so i'm literally
going to get this same move just copy
and paste it right here nothing changes
i'm just simply repeating what the past
has done right so if price comes into
this area right here where it is right
now and it just continues melting like
it just continues to drop that's cool
fine i'm gonna wait for it at my next
area of interest which would be around
this level here and we'll be honest if
this drops to 12 000
this is gonna be crazy there's gonna be
a show so i'm gonna personally wait for
it to come into this resistance
resistance resistance resistance and
then they have it used as support around
this area where i'm gonna definitely be
looking for buys into the next structure
point where it can reject
so if price were to come into this level
of support resistance resistance
resistance then is when i will be
looking because it's just the most
logical sense once price comes into this
area what are the probabilities that it
goes up rather than down probably higher
right because we're above the level like
we're above the floor so it's destined
to head to the upside this is kind of
where i'm going to basically be looking
to uh potentially be looking for buys
obviously if i get my rejection signals
and then what i would do is i would wait
for my take profit to be hit at this
next level resistance because again
price could simply come into this level
and then reject how we've done in the
past and same exact example as i placed
right here at 30 000 if price does
happen to close above i will then wait
for the retest to then continue to the
upside this is very simple this is me
not knowing if they're printing bitcoin
if they're stealing bitcoin if whatever
is going on with bitcoin i'm just purely
basing it off of technical analysis you
can see all of my other videos where i
literally go over technical analysis on
forex pairs and it works the same exact
way perfect it doesn't matter if the
great british pound is being printed if
there's covid it's all market structure
so um if you guys found this video
useful i know i'm not a crypto guy it's
on my forks guys you know you know if
this helps you guys makes more sense
drop a comment if you guys want to see
more crypto coins or more crypto videos
kind of like on the things that i'm
involved in drop a comment make sure to
like comment and subscribe and i'll see
you in this friday's podcast so take it
easy guys and i will see you then